let triviaQuestions = [

    {question: "Where did Meredith Grey go to College?", 
        answers: ["Darmouth College", "Princeton University" , "Prescott College" , "Stanford University"],
        theAnswer: 0,
    },
    
    {question: "What does Cristina Yang call Alex Karev?",
        answers: ["Her Person" , "Evil Spawn" , "Four" , "Trash Can"], 
        theAnswer: 1,
    },

    {question: "Which intern was pregnant at age 16?",
        answers: ["Meredith Grey" , "Lexie Grey" , "Isabell Stevens" , "Miranda Bailey"], 
        theAnswer: 2,
    },

    {question: "What was the name of the first episode?",
        answers: ["'Band-aid Covers the Bullet Hole'", "'A Hard Day's Night'" , "'The First Cut is the Deepest'" ,  "'Raindrop Keeps Falling on My Head'"], 
        theAnswer: 1,
    },

    {question: "What is the name of the hospital Meredith works?",
        answers: ["Mercy West", "Seattle West", "Mercy Grace", "Seattle Grace"], 
        theAnswer: 3,
    },

    {question: "What is the name of the bar the doctors hang out in?",
        answers: [ "Emerald City Bar", "Southern Nights", "Ember", "The Lodge"], 
        theAnswer: 0,
    },

    {question: "Who left Cristina Yang at the alter?",
        answers: [ "Derek Shepherd", "Preston Burke", "George O'Malley", "Alex Karev"],
        theAnswer: 1,
    },

    {question: "What is the name that Alex Karev gives the woman he saved from the ferry accident?",
        answers: [ "Reed", "Rebecca", "Miranda", "Ava"], 
        theAnswer: 3,
    },

    {question: "Finish this phrase: You will always be my _______.",
        answers: ["Lover", "Friend", "Person", "Wife"], 
        theAnswer: 2,
    },

    {question: "What is the name that Alex Karev gives the woman he saved from the ferry accident?",
        answers: ["'It’s a beautiful day to save lives.'", "'You will always be my person.'", "'Pick me. Choose me. Love me.'", "'You were like coming up for fresh air.'"],
        theAnswer: 0,
    },

    {question: "What nickname do the interns give Derek Shephard?",
        answers: ["McDreamy", "McSteamy", "McHottie", "McBitchy"], 
        theAnswer: 0,
    },

    {question: "What is Meredith Grey’s sister’s name? ",
        answers: ["Ellis Grey", "Courtney Grey", "Lexie Grey",  "Rebecca Grey"],
        theAnswer: 2,
    }

] // triviaQuestions end bracket